Tomy Krisna Permadi

+6285254451922 - tommykrisna7@gmail.com



WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2021 - present

TECH DEV SECTION HEAD

Youtap Indonesia

In this role, I develop Youtap Portal, Youtap Online Order, Youtap BOS, payment system, integration with third-party systems, manage teams, deliver applications according to schedule, improve features, and perform maintenance.

Job Description:

- **Software Developer**: Develop software according to needs using (Node.js, NestJS, MySQL, ReactJS, Angular, Ionic, Go).
- Lead Front End And Back End Team: Determine the technology used, motivate the team, divide the work.
- **Reporting**: Report progress to management and other teams.
- Analysis Requirement Feature: Analyze software requirements before developing standard features or custom features.
- **Development Review**: Review code and ensure development is in accordance with requirements.
- **Project Apps**: Youtap Portal, Youtap Online Order, Youtap API, Youtap Bos web, Youtap Bos Android & IOS, Internal CMS.

Jan 2019 - Aug 2021

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / SUPERVISOR

PT. PEOPLE INTELLIGENCE INDONESIA

In here, I'm focus to develop greatdayhr app,manage team, deliver apps to client, custom, enchance feature, reset and so many other.

JOB DESCRIPTION:

- **Software Developer**: development software by requirement use (nodejs, angular, ionic, mysql, kotlin, java, nestjs).
- Lead Team : Management timeline team and management team work flow
- Reporting: Report Progress to management and other team
- Analysis Requirement Feature : Analysis requirement software before development standar feature or custom feature
- **Development Review** : Review after development finish to make sure delivering feature to client or release
- Project Apps: Greatday HR, Greatday Lite, Greatday Kiosk, Greatday Thermal
- **Module** : Page Builder, flexible Benefit, Attendance, Leave, Overtime, On Duty , and Custom Feature

Dec 2017 - Dec 2018

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

VISIONET DATA INTERNATIONAL

Here I have complete some IT project, leader and I'm focus develop engine 5 app.

www.kalibrr.com Page 1 of 5

JOB DESCRIPTION:

• Software Developer : development software by

requirement use (angular).
• **Project**: Engine 5 apps

Jan 2017 - Dec 2018

DEVELOPER / LEAD

CV. SAKRAL TECHNOLOGY

Here I have completed several IT projects such as creating a company website, and some company systems

JOB DESCRIPTION:

- Software Developer: development software by requirement use (nodejs, angular).
- Lead Team: Management timeline team and management team work flow
- Reporting: Report Progress to management and other team
- Analysis Requirement : Analysis requirement software before development
- Development Review: Review after development finish to make sure delivering feature
- Project: system informasi Pemkab. Raja ampat, system rumah sakit benmari

Feb 2016 - Dec 2017

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

JASA WEB MALANG

Here I have completed several IT projects such as creating a company website, and some company systems.

JOB DESCRIPTION:

- Web Developer: development software by requirement use (php, angular, java)
- Lead Team : Management timeline team and management team work flow
- Reporting : Report Progress to management and client
- Analysis Requirement : Analysis requirement software before development
- Development Review : Review after development finish to make sure delivering feature
- **Project**: System Pariwisata Sawahlunto, System internal Center Of Study For Indonesian Leadership.

Jan 2016 - Mar 2016

internship

PT. VARMATEL

Here I have complete some IT project, leader and I'm focus develop engine 5 app.

JOB DESCRIPTION:

- build website company profile to which can be used for marketing
- · create documentation system
- · report daily work

Jan 2011 - Jun 2011

internship

DINAS PENDIDIKAN KAB.NABIRE

Job Description:

- manage school database in nabire
- support school find and manage student data
- create latter to make submission

EDUCATION

www.kalibrr.com
Page 2 of 5

Jan 2009 - Jan 2009 SMK N 1 NABIRE

Majoring Science: Teknik Komputer dan Jaringan (TKJ)

Jan 2012 - Jan 2012 Information Technology

Universitas Brawijaya (Brawijaya University)

Majoring Information System, Faculty of Information Technology GPA 3.03/4.00

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Learn and exploring in the field of Information System & Technology since 2009. Has been in the world of professionals since 2014 and have manage, lead, complete projects with various kind of software products and services since then. Always motivated, excited and feel challenged to learn new things.

Able to see potential business value on the product being developed from internal and external factors to enrich business model. Able to think out of the box for problem solving purposes. Able to manage and motivate the teams to work well together.

SKILLS

- Software Development
- Database
- Software Project Management
- Ecommerce
- HRIS
- Payment System

SEMINARS AND TRAININGS

Dec 2019 Angular and Ionic Basic

Associated with PT. Indodev Niaga Internet

Dec 2022 NodeJS Basic & Frameworks

Associated with PT. Indodev Niaga Internet

PROJECTS

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022 Amman Wordpress Based Website

Project Manager

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022 MOCUCIMOBILKU

Front End Developer

manage team, manage timeline, development (typescript, angular, nestjs, ionic, mysql)

Sep 2022 - Nov 2022 Redesign, Development & Implementation PTAR Public Website

Project Manager

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022 PTAR – Website Migration to New Server

Project Manager

Jul 2022 - Aug 2022 Content Update and Layout AMMAN Website Page

Project Manager

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022 1 Year Maintenance Amman Wordpress Based Website

Project Manager

Menage team, meet with client, maintenance website (php, vue)

May 2022 - Jul 2022 Intranet Web Portal Enchancement

Project Manager

www.kalibrr.com Page 3 of 5

May 2022 - Jul 2022	Kirby Web Portal Project Manager
May 2022 - May 2022	SCDF Workplan Seminar 2022 Developer front end developers (typescript, react, nextjs)
Apr 2022 - May 2022	Army Open House 2022 Developer front end developers (react, nextjs)
Apr 2022 - Apr 2022	PERFOMANCE MONITORING DASHBOARD WEB APPLICATION Project Manager
Feb 2022 - Mar 2022	Singapore Aerospace Technology Leadership Forum 2022 Developer front end developers (typescript, react, nextjs)
Jan 2022 - Feb 2022	Travel Agent Industry Forum 2022 Developer
Oct 2021 - Dec 2021	front end developers (typescript, react, nextjs) htx cms 2021 Developer front end developers (react, nextjs)
Dec 2021 - Dec 2021	Kiehls Retinol 2021 Developer front end developers (typescript, react, nextjs)
Dec 2021 - Dec 2021	Requirement Gathering & Analysis Trac Corporate Apps – Phase 2 Companion
Oct 2021 - Nov 2021	Meta Women in Sports 2021 Developer front end developers (typescript, react, nextjs)
Aug 2021 - Oct 2021	nars-website-2021 Developer front end developers (svelte, react, nextjs)
Sep 2021 - Oct 2021	YSL Beaute Records 2021 Developer front end developers (typescript, react, nextjs)
Aug 2021 - Oct 2021	Hydeout World 2021 Website Developer front end developers (react, nextjs)
Feb 2019 - Nov 2019	Siafu Shop Internal System Management

u www.kalibrr.com Page 4 of 5

Project Manager

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (typescript, angular, nestjs, kotlin, mysgl)

Feb 2019 - Nov 2019 Siafu Shop Warehouse

Project Manager

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (typescript, angular, nestjs, kotlin, mysgl)

Feb 2019 - Nov 2019 Siafu Shop Store Mnagement System

Project Manager

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (typescript, angular, nestjs, kotlin, mysql)

Feb 2019 - Nov 2019 Siafu Shop Ecommerce

Project manager

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (typescript, angular, nestjs, kotlin, mysgl)

Feb 2019 - Nov 2019 Learning Project Mobile Apps

Project Manager

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (typescript, angular, nestjs, ionic, mysql)

Apr 2017 - Jun 2017 Marketing System PT Gunung Harta Solution

Developer and lead

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (php, laravel, mysql)

Jan 2017 - Mar 2017 Pembukuan Barang Balai Besar Insemidasi Buatan

Software Developer Lead

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (php, laravel, mysql, wrdpress)

Mar 2017 - Mar 2017 System Lembaga Penyediaan Tenaga Angkatan Laut

Software Developer / lead

meet with client, manage team, manage timeline, development (php, laravel, mysql)

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Aug 2017 Learn SEO For Wordpress Websites

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-BJWVUL6T/

Aug 2017 PMI-ACP Certification: The Scrum Development Process

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-IC89LMLG/

www.kalibrr.com Page 5 of 5